http://explorehimalaya.com/privacy-policy-updated

under
Company News,
20SHARESShareTweet
Privacy Policy
Effective date: August 20, 2019 Explore Himalaya (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.explorehimalaya.com/ website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for Explore Himalaya is created with the help of the Free Privacy Policy Generator.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.explorehimalaya.com/
Information Collection And Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address
Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
Explore Himalaya uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain the Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer care and support
To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
To monitor the usage of the Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer Of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside Nepal and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Nepal and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
Explore Himalaya will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure Of Data
Legal Requirements
Explore Himalaya may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of Explore Himalaya
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security Of Data
The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: it@explorehimalaya.com
« How to Train Yourself for Everest Base Camp Trek?
|
How to Train Mentally for Everest Base Camp Trek »
Post a comment
Click here to cancel reply.
Name
Email
Message
Got tourism news & events to be featured?
Email: updates@explorehimalaya.com
Subscribe to Updates
Email*
EmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
Recent Posts
Explore Himalaya President Suman Pandey Elected Secretary/Treasurer of PATABird Watching And Photography Tour with Andy TeasdaleIsland Peak Trek & Climbing CourseOh Eun-Sun becomes the first woman to summit the 14 highest peaksFishtail Air’s Rescue Operation in Manaslu Himal
Categories
ArchitectureBlogEquipments and GadgetsClimbing & ExpeditionsCommunity Service ProjectCompany NewsCulture & FestivalsFood & AccommodationInterviewsLuxury ToursPhoto EssaySkydiveSpecial EventsTestimonialTourism NewsTravel GuideTrekking & HikingTrip ReportWildlife & Bird Watching
Archive
Select Month
October 2020  (1)
July 2020  (1)
March 2020  (6)
February 2020  (5)
January 2020  (2)
December 2019  (3)
November 2019  (6)
September 2019  (4)
July 2019  (1)
June 2019  (1)
May 2019  (1)
April 2019  (2)
March 2019  (3)
February 2019  (1)
January 2019  (3)
December 2018  (3)
November 2018  (2)
October 2018  (2)
September 2018  (2)
August 2018  (4)
July 2018  (3)
April 2018  (1)
March 2018  (2)
February 2018  (1)
January 2018  (5)
December 2017  (3)
November 2017  (3)
October 2017  (3)
September 2017  (2)
July 2017  (3)
May 2017  (2)
April 2017  (4)
December 2016  (1)
November 2016  (2)
October 2016  (4)
September 2016  (6)
August 2016  (5)
July 2016  (1)
June 2016  (5)
May 2016  (15)
April 2016  (8)
March 2016  (10)
February 2016  (10)
January 2016  (15)
December 2015  (9)
November 2015  (11)
October 2015  (6)
September 2015  (9)
August 2015  (10)
July 2015  (15)
June 2015  (11)
May 2015  (17)
April 2015  (5)
March 2015  (6)
February 2015  (3)
January 2015  (2)
December 2014  (7)
November 2014  (2)
September 2014  (5)
August 2014  (7)
July 2014  (2)
June 2014  (4)
May 2014  (5)
April 2014  (17)
March 2014  (17)
February 2014  (8)
January 2014  (12)
December 2013  (7)
November 2013  (15)
October 2013  (22)
September 2013  (8)
August 2013  (6)
July 2013  (7)
June 2013  (2)
May 2013  (12)
April 2013  (19)
March 2013  (19)
February 2013  (21)
January 2013  (52)
December 2012  (50)
November 2012  (26)
October 2012  (3)
August 2012  (5)
July 2012  (11)
June 2012  (18)
May 2012  (26)
April 2012  (31)
March 2012  (29)
February 2012  (11)
January 2012  (14)
December 2011  (15)
November 2011  (15)
October 2011  (12)
September 2011  (5)
August 2011  (2)
July 2011  (9)
June 2011  (10)
May 2011  (21)
April 2011  (25)
March 2011  (29)
February 2011  (18)
January 2011  (21)
December 2010  (18)
November 2010  (16)
October 2010  (22)
September 2010  (18)
August 2010  (21)
July 2010  (29)
June 2010  (35)
May 2010  (37)
April 2010  (17)
March 2010  (12)
February 2010  (5)
January 2010  (8)
December 2009  (11)
November 2009  (9)
October 2009  (11)
September 2009  (4)
August 2009  (10)
July 2009  (8)
June 2009  (14)
May 2009  (14)
April 2009  (11)
March 2009  (10)
February 2009  (8)
January 2009  (17)
December 2008  (4)
November 2008  (4)
October 2008  (27)
September 2008  (11)
August 2008  (6)
July 2008  (7)
June 2008  (4)
May 2008  (4)
April 2008  (9)
March 2008  (11)
February 2008  (6)
January 2008  (4)
December 2007  (13)
November 2006  (1)
October 2006  (1)
Happy Explorers
I had dreamt about this trip my whole life. My dream was realized during these 15 days. This was one of the most important events in my life! Thank you!
- Russia
Read Testimonials | Submit Your Testimonial
Community Service
We work with the motto "Tourism for Development". Explore Himalaya Community Service Project was conceived to empower underprivileged segments of Nepal.
Join our community services
Explore Himalaya
Subscribe to updates & offers
Email*
NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
© 1997 - 2020 All Right Reserved. Explore Himalaya Travel & Adventure
Hi ! How may we be of service !
×
